
export const _2024_Questions_1 = [
  {
    name: 'Mixolomoji',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: '\nğŸ”¥ğŸ«', size: '22vh', answer: 'Hot Chocolate'}, 
      {points: 200, question: '\nğŸŠğŸğŸğŸªµğŸŒ¿', size: '22vh', answer: 'Wassail'},
      {points: 300, question: '\nğŸ„ğŸ¥Š', size: '21vh', answer: 'Christmas Punch'}, 
      {points: 400, question: '\nğŸŒµğŸ¥šğŸ§ ', size: '21vh', answer:'Spiked Eggnog'},
      {points: 500, question: '\nğŸ«ğŸ·', size: '22vh', answer: 'Mulled Wine'},
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Fa-la-la-la Fauna',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: "\nThe Grinch's\ndog / reindeer?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Max'}, 
      {points: 200, question: "\nFormerly unemployed navigator reindeer?", size: '14vh', answer: "Rudolph"}, 
      {points: 300, question: "\nThe Nutcracker's towering nemesis?", size: '16vh', answer: 'The Mouse / Rat King'}, 
      {points: 400, question: "\nHalloween Town's bestest boy?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Zero'}, 
      {points: 500, question: "____ the extended auditory appendaged ungulate?", size: '18vh', answer: 'Nestor'}, 
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Christmas Casting',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: "The Grinch in\nâ€œHow The Grinch Stole Christmas\"\n(2000)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Jim Carrey'}, 
      {points: 200, question: "The Conductor in\nâ€œThe Polar Express\"\n(2004)", size: '16vh', answer: "Tom Hanks"}, 
      {points: 300, question: "George Bailey in\nâ€œItâ€™s a Wonderful Lifeâ€\n(1946) ", size: '16vh', answer: 'Jimmy Stewart'}, 
      {points: 400, question: "Kate McCallister in\nâ€œHome Aloneâ€\n(1990)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Catherine O\'Haram'}, 
      {points: 500, question: "Shelter manager Karen Allen in â€œScroogedâ€\n(1988)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Karen Allen'}, 
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Holiday Hodgepodge',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: "What â€œspyâ€ hides around the house, telling Santa who has been naughty and nice? Elf on a Shelf?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Elf on a Shelf'}, 
      {points: 200, question: "What color are the berries of mistletoe?", size: '16vh', answer: 'White'}, 
      {points: 300, question: "Which Christmas song was the first song broadcast in space?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Jingle Bells'}, 
      {points: 400, question: "Which arid U.S. state is the home to the town of Snowflake?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Arizona'}, 
      {points: 500, question: "In what year did Edison Co. VP Edward Johnson decorate a tree with the first electric Christmas lights? (Closest wins)", size: '13vh', answer: '1882'}
    ]
  }
];

export const _2024_Questions_2 = [
  {
    name: 'Mixolomoji',
    rows: [
      { points: 100, question: '\nğŸ cy+ğŸšª', size: '22vh', answer: 'Apple Cider' },
      { points: 200, question: '\nğŸŒ¶ï¸ğŸ¬ ğŸ®+ca', size: '22vh', answer: 'Peppermint Mocha' },
      { points: 300, question: '\nğŸŒ®ğŸ”¥ğŸ«', size: '22vh', answer: 'Mexican Hot Chocolate' },
      { points: 400, question: '\nğŸ”¥ğŸ§ˆ ğŸƒâ€â™‚ï¸-n+m', size: '21vh', answer: 'Hot Buttered Rum' },
      { points: 500, question: '\nğŸ˜¾ and ğŸ­ (names)', size: '21vh', answer: 'Tom and Jerry' },
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Fa-la-la-la Fauna',
    rows: [
      { points: 100, question: "\nBright and starry reindeer?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Comet' },
      { points: 200, question: "\nRobbie the reindeer's nemesis?", size: '14vh', answer: "Blitzen" },
      { points: 300, question: "\nDecorates his doghouse with Christmas lights?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Snoopy' },
      { points: 400, question: "\nHouse-invading turkey-eating hounds?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Bumpus\'s hound dogs' },
      { points: 500, question: "Lost penguin from\nâ€œSanta Claus is Comin' to Townâ€", size: '18vh', answer: 'Topper' },
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Christmas Casting',
    rows: [
      { points: 100, question: "Ebenezer Scrooge in\nâ€œThe Muppet Christmas Carol\" (1992)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Michael Caine' },
      { points: 200, question: "Jovie in\nâ€œElf\"\n(2003)", size: '16vh', answer: "Zooey Deschanel" },
      { points: 300, question: "Gus Polinkski in\nâ€œHome Aloneâ€\n(1990)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Johny Candy' },
      { points: 400, question: "Overworked assistant Grace Cooley in â€œScroogedâ€\n(1988)", size: '16vh', answer: 'Alfre Woodard' },
      { points: 500, question: "Mrs. Parker in\nâ€œA Christmas Storyâ€\n(1983) ", size: '16vh', answer: 'Melinda Dillon' },
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Holiday Hodgepodge',
    rows: [
      { points: 100, question: "How many ghosts show themselves to Scrooge in the original A Christmas Carol?", size: '14vh', answer: '4 (Marley, Past, Present, and Future)' },
      { points: 200, question: "What was Frosty the Snowmanâ€™s nose made out of?", size: '16vh', answer: 'A button' },
      { points: 300, question: "What hymn was written by a Pastor when a church organ broke?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Silent Night' },
      { points: 400, question: "Which Nordic country donates the Christmas tree in London's Trafalgar Square?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Norway' },
      { points: 500, question: "The bones of St. Nicholas of Myra were stolen in 1087 by sailors from this Mediterranean country?", size: '13vh', answer: 'Italy, from the city of Bari' }
    ]
  }
];

export const _2025_Questions_1 = [
      {
        name: 'Yummoji',
        rows: [
          {points: 100, question: '\nğŸ¦ƒğŸ¦†ğŸ“', size: '22vh', answer: 'Turducken'}, 
          {points: 200, question: '\nğŸ„ğŸªµ', size: '22vh', answer: 'Yule Log'},
          {points: 300, question: '\nğŸ«šğŸğŸ‘¨', size: '22vh', answer: 'Gingerbread Man'},
          {points: 400, question: '\nğŸŒ¶ï¸ğŸ¬ğŸ¶', size: '21vh', answer: 'Peppermint Bark'}, 
          {points: 500, question: '\nğŸƒğŸ”‘ğŸ’©ğŸ›ï¸', size: '21vh', answer:'Figgy Pudding'},
        ]
      },
      {
        name: 'Holiday Horror',
        rows: [
          {points: 100, question: "What fossil fuel does Santa famously leave for \"naughty\" children?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Coal'}, 
          {points: 200, question: " In the song \"Itâ€™s the Most Wonderful Time of the Year,\" what 'scary' thing are people doing?", size: '14vh', answer: "Telling ghost stories"}, 
          {points: 300, question: "What horned, Alpine \"Anti-Santa\" carries a sack to kidnap misbehaving kids?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Krampus'}, 
          {points: 400, question: "In 1908, which industry began officially designating candle-lit Christmas trees as an 'unacceptable risk'?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Fire insurance industry'}, 
          {points: 500, question: "The predatory JÃ³lakÃ¶tturinn is a holiday monster from which Atlantic island nation?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Iceland'}, 
        ]
      },
      {
        name: 'Misleading Melodies',
        rows: [
          {points: 100, question: "\"I Saw Three Ships\" states a trio of vessels sailed into which landlocked Holy Land city?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Bethlehem'}, 
          {points: 200, question: "Which winter-winter-winter anthem was composed in the middle of a July 1945 heatwave?", size: '14vh', answer: "Let it Snow! Let it Snow! Let it Snow!"}, 
          {points: 300, question: "In 1780, there were four \"colly birds\" (not calling birds) which were what color?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Black'}, 
          {points: 400, question: "\"How All the Welkin Rings\" was the original 1739 line of what Christmas hymn?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Hark! The Herald Angels Sing'}, 
          {points: 500, question: "Which Christmas melody originated as the 1901 Ukrainian New Yearâ€™s folk chant \"Shchedryk\"?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Carol of the Bells'}, 
        ]
      },
      {
        name: 'Christmas Crime',
        rows: [
          {points: 100, question: "In the movie Home Alone, the \"Wet Bandits\" earn their nickname by doing what to every house they burgle?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Leaving the water running'}, 
          {points: 200, question: "A man dressed in a Santa suit robbed a San Francisco bank in Dec 2014, using what annual event to blend in and escape?", size: '14vh', answer: "SantaCon"}, 
          {points: 300, question: "Until 1991, it was technically illegal to celebrate Christmas in which Caribbean island nation?", size: '16vh', answer: 'Cuba'}, 
          {points: 400, question: "In 1826, 21 cadets at which military academy were punished for smuggling alcoholic eggnog into a barracks?", size: '14vh', answer: 'West Point'}, 
          {points: 500, question: "In 1659, which North American colony passed a law making Christmas a criminal offense, punishable by a fine of five shillings?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Massachusetts'}, 
        ]
      },
      {
        name: 'Holiday Hodgepodge',
        rows: [
          {points: 100, question: "Famous animator Chuck Jones recolored which holiday villain to green for the 1966 TV special?", size: '14vh', answer: 'The Grinch (from b&w)'}, 
          {points: 200, question: "Legend says a German choirmaster created what treat in 1670 to keep children quiet during long church services?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Candy Cane'}, 
          {points: 300, question: "To deliver presents to every household on Earth in one night, physicists estimate Santa would have to travel at roughly 0.5% of what measure?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Speed of light'}, 
          {points: 400, question: "According to the Guinness World Records, the tallest Christmas tree ever displayed was a 221 ft. Douglas Fir erected in 1950 in what rainy city?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Seattle'}, 
          {points: 500, question: "What is the highest-grossing Christmas movie of all time (when adjusted for inflation), at a cool $1.2 billion?", size: '14vh', answer: 'Home Alone'}
        ]
      }
    ]
    ;